{
    "subject": "resource/Doctor_Who",
    "predicate": "property/related",
    "object": "resource/K-9_(TV_series)",
    "human_readable": "Doctor Who is related to K-9 (TV series).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8064309358596802,
            "question": "What is the connection between Doctor Who and K-9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.762696385383606,
            "question": "Is Doctor Who a television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7585614323616028,
            "question": "Who or what is associated with K-9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.740013062953949,
            "question": "What type of media features both Doctor Who and K-9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7110395431518555,
            "question": "What is K-9 related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6001704335212708,
            "question": "Can you name a fictional character who appears in a TV series alongside K-9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.400313138961792,
            "question": "Besides being a character in a TV series, what else might K-9 be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04438520595431328,
            "question": "Is there a famous robot companion associated with a science fiction TV show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.036449287086725235,
            "question": "What is the name of the iconic science fiction television series featuring a Time Lord?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01909828744828701,
            "question": "Which fictional character often travels through time and space in a TARDIS?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Doctor Who is related to K-9 (TV series).",
            "html": "dbpedia_4654_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the iconic science fiction television series featuring a Time Lord?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4654_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a famous robot companion associated with a science fiction TV show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4654_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides being a character in a TV series, what else might K-9 be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4654_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_174.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4654_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms the relation between \"Doctor Who\" and \"K-9,\" indicating they are associated through the context of a TV series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}